

Irina Ziborova

Graphic and Web Designer

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ziborovairina

Portfolio: irinaziborova.de Location: Berlin, Germany

irisha.ziborova@gmail.com | +79 213939464 | Skype: irazib

Personal Statement

I want to design, layout and implement modern and user-friendly web sites being part of a collaborative and dynamic team. As a Master graduate in Computer Graphics and Web Design, my profile merges design expertise with coding skills, and a solid background on UX design.

Skills

Graphic Design: Photoshop, Illustrator, CorelDraw, GIF animation, video editing, After Effects, Sketch, InDesign, Zeplin, AXURE, InVision **Web Design**: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Github

Work Experience

UI Designer at Netcracker

November 2017 - Present, St. Petersburg, Russia

- Create user flows in AXURE, Photoshop and InVision for a big telecommunication company portal.
- Collaborate with customers and business analyst.
- Design tasks for graph tools.

Web Designer at Avanta Digital

June 2017 - November 2017, St. Petersburg, Russia

- Created websites, content, service designs and user scenarios.
- Collaborated with customers, front-end and back-end developers.
- Biggest achievement: Created the whole design and graphics for a big clothing online shop in a short time from zero.

Project Coordinator at Reksoft

Feb 2012 - May 2017, St. Petersburg, Russia

- Coordinated software development projects, communicated with developers, suppliers and customers.
- Assisted in the development of user interfaces.
- Biggest achievement: Coordination of a large-scale airport baggage sorting system project with a volume of 1.5M Euro.

Freelance Projects

UX Researcher at Lokal

Sep 2016 – Dec 2016, Helsinki, Finland

- Conducted research in the field of user experience (UX).
- Created wireframes, storyboards, user workflows and processes (mind map, affinity diagrams, user groups, personas and behavior scenarios).

Graphic Designer at Level Jewel

Apr 2016 - May 2016, St. Petersburg, Russia

- Created icons and graphic materials for the social networks.
- Conducted design and usability consultations of better content and graphic creation.
- Created a press page for the website.

Education

Master Degree, ITMO University

Sep 2015 – Jun 2017, St. Petersburg, Russia

- Master in Computer Graphics and Web Design, GPA: 5A (highest)
- Courses: Technologies in Website Creation, User Interface Construction, User-centered Methods for Product and Service Design, Design of WWW Services, Typography, and others.

Semester Abroad, Aalto University

Aug 2016 - Dec 2016, Helsinki, Finland

• Master in Computer, Communication and Information Sciences

Bachelor Degree, State Polytechnic University

Aug 2009 - Dec 2015, St. Petersburg, Russia

Bachelor in Management, Computer Science with honors,
GPA: 4.7 (5 is the highest)

Conferences and Publications

XIV Scientific Conference ITMO

 Presented my paper "Features of Prototyping Interfaces in the Field of Education"

Science Week SPBSTU

 Presented my paper "Improving the Management of Small Businesses in the Municipalities by Implementing Modern Information Technologies"

Languages

Russian (native), English (C1), German (currently studying A2/B1 level)

References

Ekaterina Zabelinskaya, Sales Director Reksoft

Reksoft Isafjordsgatan, 39B 16440, Kista, Sweden Phone: +46 8 500 083 21, e-mail: rfi@reksoft.se

Ekaterina Egoshina, Marketing Director, ITMO University

Innovation activity marketing department ITMO University, Kronverskiy pr. 49, St. Petersburg, Russia Phone: +7 (812) 457-18-04; e-mail: eegoshina@corp.ifmo.ru